https://www.snowtechmagazine.com/privacy-policy/

0
Best Value in Snowmobiling! Great winter experiences with friends...
Tim Bender and his Yamaha Vmax-4 Formula III Race Sled
Nov 21, 2020
3
INSIDE THE HALL OF FAME: MAN AND MACHINE –...
A Hidden Gem in the Touring Segment?
Oct 15, 2020
1
2020 Yamaha RS Venture TF – 2,938 Mile Test...
2021 Ski-Doo MX Z X-RS 1,300 Mile Test Report
Oct 8, 2020
0
When Ski-Doo introduced their new Gen 4 REV platform,...
0
Best Value in Snowmobiling! Great winter experiences with friends...
Tim Bender and his Yamaha Vmax-4 Formula III Race Sled
Nov 21, 2020
3
INSIDE THE HALL OF FAME: MAN AND MACHINE –...
A Hidden Gem in the Touring Segment?
Oct 15, 2020
1
2020 Yamaha RS Venture TF – 2,938 Mile Test...
2021 Ski-Doo MX Z X-RS 1,300 Mile Test Report
Oct 8, 2020
0
When Ski-Doo introduced their new Gen 4 REV platform,...
Privacy Policy
SnowTechMagazine.com Privacy Policy
SnowTechMagazine.com recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of all information provided by our customers. We created this policy out of respect for our customers, web site visitors and vendors who may use this site. Vintagesleds.com collects information from our web site users, and customers. The following is a description of the type of information we collect and how we use it to provide better services to our customers.
Communications to SnowTechMagazine.com
When using our web site and filling in forms to contact us, or for support or service inquires, users are required to give some contact information, such as your name, company, email address, mailing address and phone number. We also may collect demographic information. For our web site visitors, we use this information to help provide a more personalized experience on our site. Demographic information is used for internal purposes to help us understand our customers better. Requests for service, support or information will be forwarded as needed to best respond to a specific request. We may retain emails and other information sent to us for our internal administrative purposes, and to help us to serve customers better.
Communications from SnowTechMagazine.com to you
In order to best serve you (our customer), we may send information about our support, services and new features. For example, we may send new members a “Welcome to SnowTechMagazine.com” message. We may also communicate with customers to provide requested service and other issues via email, phone or regular “snail” mail.
We sometimes offer our customers the option to receive information about our company, related products, services and special deals.
You will always have the choice not to receive these communications from us, if requested.
Email Newsletter
If users wish to subscribe to our email newsletter, we ask for contact information (such as name, e-mail address and, occasionally, demographic information). We use this information in the same manner as we use contact information in the Web Site Forms described above. Recipients of our newsletters can unsubscribe using the instructions listed at the end of the email newsletter.
Surveys, Contests and Promotional Services
From time to time we may invite users to provide information for either a survey, contest or Promotional Service. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether to disclose requested contact information and demographic information. In addition to other uses set forth in this policy, contact information collected in connection with surveys and contests is used to notify the winners and award prizes, to monitor or improve the use and satisfaction of the site.
Interactive Features
From time to time, SnowTechMagazine.com may offer interactive and community features such as discussion boards, webcasts and the ability to respond to web logs. Note that all personal information sent or posted via such features will (depending on the feature) become public information for which we are not responsible. Please note that any posts made to the web site by a user are subject to deletion at the will of SnowTechMagazine.com for any reason.
Automatic Data Collection
Our web site may have features that automatically collect information from visitors to deliver content specific to users’ interests and to honor their preferences. This information assists us in creating sites that will better serve the needs of our visitors. We may use “cookies,” a file with a small amount of data that is stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Cookies benefit the user by saving time while on our site. If users reject the cookies, some portions of the site may not work for you. Additionally, we may have some of the pages a user visits on our site collect data through the use of “pixel tags”. Cookies and pixels tags allow us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. To measure the use of our web site for internal use, we gather items such as the date, time, browser type, navigation history and IP address of all visitors to our site. This information does not contain anything that can identify users personally.
Sharing of your information
SnowTechMagazine.com will not share your information with anyone else. We do not share personally identifiable information with other companies, apart from those acting as our agents in providing our product(s)/service(s), and which agree to use it only for that purpose and to keep the information secure and confidential. Entities into which our company may be merged, or entities to which any of our assets, products, sites or operations may be transferred, will be able to use personal information. We will also disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena or other legal obligation, in response to a law enforcement agency’s request, or in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property. Users should also be aware that courts of equity, such as U.S. Bankruptcy Courts, might have the authority under certain circumstances to permit personal information to be shared or transferred to third parties without permission. We may share aggregate information, which is not personally identifiable, with others. This information may include usage and demographic data, but it will not include personal information.
Security
We use reasonable precautions to protect our users’ personal information and to store it securely. Access to all of our users’ information, is restricted. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. Finally, the servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Links
Our web site contain links to other sites. SnowTechMagazine.com cannot be held responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites.
Changes to this policy
SnowTechMagazine.com may, from time to time, revisit this policy.
Add a comment
No comments so far.
Be first to leave comment below.
Cancel replyYour email address will not be published. Required fields are marked *Post comment
